embedsocial.com 2019-05-23

# Privacy Policy - EmbedSocial

_Effective date: May 23, 2018_

EmbedSocial PLTD (“EmbedSocial”, “us”, “we”, and/or “our”) operates the embedsocial.com website and platform (“Service”).

The Privacy Policy informs you of our policies regarding the collection, use, and disclosure of personally identifiable data (“Personal Data”) when you use our Service and the choices you have associated with that data.

We use your data to provide and improve the Service. By using the Service, you agree to the collection and use of information in accordance with this policy. Unless otherwise defined in this Privacy Policy, terms used in this Privacy Policy have the same meanings as in our Terms and Conditions, accessible from EmbedSocial.com

#### 1\. Information That You Provide To Us

##### Account and Registration Information:

We ask for and may collect personal information about you such as your name, address, email address, as well as certain related information like your company name and website name, when you register for an account to access or utilize one or more of our Services (an “Account”). We also ask for and collect personal information such as an email address and a name or alias from any individual that you authorize to log into and utilize our Services in connection with Your Account.

A third-party intermediary Recurly is used to manage credit card processing. This intermediary is not permitted to store, retain, or use your billing information for any purpose except for credit card processing on our behalf. You can find their privacy policy here: <https://recurly.com/legal/privacy>  
We refer to any information described above as “Account Information” for the purposes of this Policy. By voluntarily providing us with Account Information, you represent that you are the owner of such personal data or otherwise have the requisite consent to provide it to us.

##### Reviews:

We may post reviews on our Service that may contain personal information. We obtain your consent to post your name along with your review. If you wish to update or delete your testimonial, you can contact us at [privacy@embedsocial.com.](mailto:privacy@embedsocial.com)

##### EmbedSocial Team Sharing:

We may share information, including personal information, with any member of the EmbedSocial team.

##### With Your Consent:

We may also share personal information with third parties when we have your consent to do so.

##### Other Submissions:

We ask for and may collect personal information from you when you submit web forms on our Websites or as you use interactive features of the Websites, including, participation in surveys, contests, promotions, sweepstakes, requesting customer support, or otherwise communicating with us.

#### 2\. Information That We Collect From You on our Websites

##### Cookies and Other Tracking Technologies:

We and our authorized partners may use cookies and other information gathering technologies for a variety of purposes. These technologies may provide us with personal information, information about devices and networks you utilize to access our Service, and other information regarding your interactions with our Service. For detailed information about the use of cookies in our Service, please read and review our Cookie Policy found here: [https://embedsocial.com/cookie-policy.](https://embedsocial.com/cookie-policy/)

We partner with third parties to either display advertising on the Websites or to manage our advertising on other sites. Our third party partners may also use technologies such as cookies to gather information about your activities on our Websites and other sites in order to suggest advertisements based upon your browsing activities and interests. If you wish to not have this information used for the purpose of serving you interest-based ads, you may opt-out by clicking [here](http://preferences-mgr.truste.com/) (or if located in the European Union you may opt-in the use of cookies, by clicking [here](http://www.youronlinechoices.eu/)).

Tags and scripts may be used on our Service or in email or other electronic communications we send to you. These assist us in delivering cookies, counting visits to our Service, understanding usage, and campaign effectiveness and determining whether an email has been opened and acted upon. We may receive reports based on the use of these technologies by our third-party service providers on an individual and aggregated basis.

##### Logs:

As is true with most websites and services delivered over the Internet, we gather certain information and store it in log files when you interact with our Service. This information includes internet protocol (IP) addresses as well as browser type, internet service provider, URLs of referring/exit pages, operating system, date/time stamp, information you search for, locale and language preferences, identification numbers associated with your devices, your mobile carrier, and system configuration information. Occasionally, we connect personal information to information gathered in our log files as necessary to improve our Service. In such a case, we would treat the combined information in accordance with this Policy.

##### Analytics:

We collect analytics information when you use our Service to help us improve them. We may also share anonymous data about your actions on our Service with third-party service providers of analytics services.

#### 3\. Information Collected From Other Sources

##### Social Media Widgets:

The Websites include social media features, such as the Facebook Like button, and widgets, such as the Share This button or interactive mini-programs that run on our Service. These features may collect your Internet protocol address, which page you are visiting on the Websites, and may set a cookie to enable the feature to function properly. Social media features and widgets are either hosted by a third party or hosted directly on our Service. Your interactions with these features are governed by the privacy statement of the companies that provide them.

##### Information From Third Party Services:

We may also obtain other information, including personal information, from third parties and combine that with information we collect through our Service. For example, we may have access to certain information from a third party social media or authentication service if you log into our Service through such a service or otherwise provide us with access to information from the service. Any access that we may have to such information from a third party social media or authentication service is in accordance with the authorization procedures determined by that service. By authorizing us to connect with a third party service, you authorize us to access and store your name, email address(es), profile picture URL, and other personal information that the third party service makes available to us, and to use and disclose it in accordance with this Policy. You should check your privacy settings on these third-party services to understand and change the information sent to us through these services. For example, you can log in to our Services using sign-in services such as Facebook Connect or Google account, as further described below.

##### Single Sign-On:

You can log into certain Services using sign-in services such as Facebook Connect or a Google account. These services will authenticate your identity, provide you with the option to share certain personal information (such as your name and email address) with us, and pre-populate our sign up form.

#### 4\. How We Use Information That We Collect

##### General Uses:

We may use the information we collect about you (including personal information, to the extent applicable) for a variety of purposes, including to (a) provide, operate, maintain, improve, and promote our Service; (b) enable you to access and use our Service; (c) process and complete transactions, and send you related information, including purchase confirmations and invoices; (d) send transactional messages, including responses to your comments, questions, and requests; provide customer service and support; and send you technical notices, updates, security alerts, and support and administrative messages; (e) send promotional communications, such as providing you with information about products and services, features, surveys, newsletters, offers, promotions, contests, and events; and provide other news or information about us and our partners. You can opt-out of receiving marketing communications from us by contacting us at [privacy@embedsocial.com](mailto:privacy@embedsocial.com) or following the unsubscribe instructions included in our marketing communications; (f) process and deliver contest or sweepstakes entries and rewards; (g) monitor and analyze trends, usage, and activities in connection with our Service and for marketing or advertising purposes; (h) investigate and prevent fraudulent transactions, unauthorized access our Service, and other illegal activities; (i) personalize our Service, including by providing features or advertisements that match your interests and preferences; and (j) for other purposes for which we obtain your consent.

##### Legal Basis for Processing (EEA only):

If you are an individual from the European Economic Area (EEA), our legal basis for collecting and using the personal information will depend on the personal information concerned and the specific context in which we collect it. However, we will normally collect personal information from you only where: (a) we have your consent to do so, (b) where we need the personal information to perform a contract with you (e.g. to deliver our Service you have requested), or (c) where the processing is in our or a third party’s legitimate interests (and not overridden by your data protection interests or fundamental rights and freedoms). In some cases, we may also have a legal obligation to collect personal information from you, or may otherwise need the personal information to protect your vital interests or those of another person.  
Where we rely on your consent to process the personal information, you have the right to withdraw or decline your consent at any time. Please note that this does not affect the lawfulness of the processing based on consent before its withdrawal.

If we ask you to provide personal information to comply with a legal requirement or to perform a contract with you, we will make this clear at the relevant time and advise you whether the provision of your personal information is mandatory or not (as well as of the possible consequences if you do not provide your personal information). Similarly, if we collect and use your personal information in reliance on our (or a third party’s) legitimate interests which are not already described in this Notice, we will make clear to you at the relevant time what those legitimate interests are.

If you have any questions about or need further information concerning the legal basis on which we collect and use your personal information, please contact us using the contact details provided further below in Section 13.

#### 5\. Sharing Of Information Collected

##### Third-Party Service Providers:

We share information, including personal information, with our third-party service providers that we use to provide hosting for and maintenance of our Service, application development, backup, storage, payment processing, analytics and other services for us. These third-party service providers may have access to or process your personal information for the purpose of providing these services for us. We do not permit our third-party service providers to use the personal information that we share with them for their marketing purposes or for any other purpose than in connection with the services they provide to us.

##### Compliance with Laws and Law Enforcement Requests; Protection of Our Rights:

In certain situations, we may be required to disclose personal information in response to lawful requests by public authorities, including to meet national security or law enforcement requirements. We may disclose personal information to respond to subpoenas, court orders, or legal process, or to establish or exercise our legal rights or defend against legal claims. We may also share such information if we believe it is necessary in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, violations of our Service Agreement, or as otherwise required by law.

#### 6\. How Long We Retain Your Personal Information

We will retain your personal information for as long as is needed to fulfill the purposes outlined in this Privacy Policy, unless a longer retention period is required or permitted by law (such as tax, accounting or other legal requirements). When we have no ongoing legitimate business need to process your personal information, we will either delete or anonymize it, or, if this is not possible (for example, because your personal information has been stored in backup archives), then we will securely store your personal information and isolate it from any further processing until deletion is possible.

For personal information that we process on behalf of our Subscribers, we will retain such personal information in accordance with the terms of our agreement with them, subject to applicable law.

#### 7\. How We Protect Your Information

The security of your information is important to us. When you enter personal information as part of our Service, we encrypt the transmission of that information using secure socket layer technology (SSL).

We use commercially reasonable physical, managerial, and technical safeguards to preserve the integrity and security of your personal information, once we receive it. For example, we continuously and regularly back up your data to help prevent data loss and aid in data recovery. No method of electronic transmission of storage is 100% secure, however, and we cannot ensure or warrant the absolute security of any information you transmit or store in the Service.

In the event that personal information is compromised as a result of a breach of security, EmbedSocial will promptly notify those persons whose personal information has been compromised, in accordance with the notification procedures set forth in this Privacy Policy, or as otherwise required by applicable law.

#### 8\. Your Rights

You have a right to be informed of Personal Information processed by EmbedSocial, a right to rectification/correction, erasure, and restriction of processing. You also have the right to receive from EmbedSocial a structured, common and machine-readable format of Personal Information you provided to us.

We can only identify you via your email address and we can only adhere to your request and provide information if we have Personal Information about you through you have made contact with us directly and/or you using our Service.

An individual who seeks access to, or who seeks to correct or, amend inaccuracies in, or delete personal information stored or processed by us on behalf of our users or customers should direct his/her query to the user/customer (the data controller). Upon receipt of a request from one of our users or customers for us to remove the data, we will respond to their request within thirty (30) days. We will retain personal information that we store and process on behalf of our users or customers for as long as needed to provide the Services to our users or customers. We will retain and use this personal information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements.

Where you have provided consent, you may withdraw it at any time, without affecting the lawfulness of the processing that was carried out prior to withdrawing it.

Whenever you withdraw consent, you acknowledge and accept that this may have a negative influence on the quality of our Service.

You further agree that EmbedSocial shall not be held liable with respect to any loss and/or damage to your Personal Information if you choose to withdraw consent.

Where Personal Information is processed for the above purposes on the basis of EmbedSocial’s legitimate interests, under the GDPR, you may object to such processing at any time. To do so please contact [privacy@embedsocial.com.](mailto:privacy@embedsocial.com)

In addition, you have the right to lodge a complaint with the data protection authority in your jurisdiction.

To exercise any of the rights mentioned in this Privacy Policy and/or in the event of questions or comments relating to the use of Personal Information you may contact EmbedSocial’s support team: [privacy@embedsocial.com.](mailto:privacy@embedsocial.com)

#### 9\. Exclusions

This Privacy Policy does not apply to any Personal Data collected by EmbedSocial other than Personal Data collected through the Service. This Privacy Policy shall not apply to any unsolicited information you provide to EmbedSocial through the Services or through any other means. This includes, but is not limited to, information posted to any public areas of the Services, such as blog post comments (collectively, “Public Areas”), any ideas for new products or modifications to existing products, and other unsolicited submissions (collectively, “Unsolicited Information”). All Unsolicited Information shall be deemed to be non-confidential and EmbedSocial shall be free to reproduce, use, disclose, and distribute such Unsolicited Information to others without limitation or attribution.

If you are invited to join an EmbedSocial team account, and you accept the invitation, you are agreeing that certain of your information will be shared with the team account holder and other team members. In particular, the team account holder will have access to your name, email address, and usage, and other team members will have access to your name, email address. Any information you share via a team account, including widgets, feeds, and albums you create or Third-Party Services you link to, will be available to all team members of the team account you have joined. You are solely responsible for any information you share via a team account, which is posted at your own risk.

#### 10\. Children’s Personal Information

We do not knowingly collect any personal information from children under the age of 13. If you are under the age of 13, please do not submit any personal information through our Service. Parents and guardians have an obligation to inform their minor children about safe and responsible handling of personal data. Minors are not allowed to give personal data without the consent of their parents or guardians. If you have reason to believe that a child under the age of 13 has provided personal information to us through our Service, please contact us at privacy@embedsocial.com, and we will use commercially reasonable efforts to delete that information.

#### 11\. Links to Other Web Sites

We are not responsible for the practices employed by websites or services linked to or from our Service, including the information or content contained therein. Please remember that when you use a link to go from our Service to another website or service, our Privacy Policy does not apply to third-party websites or services. Your browsing and interaction on any third-party website or service, including those that have a link or advertisement on our website, are subject to that third party’s own rules and policies.

#### 12\. Business Transactions

We may assign or transfer this Policy, as well as your account and related information and data, including any personal information, to any person or entity that acquires all or substantially all of our business, stock or assets, or with whom we merge.

#### 13\. Changes To This Privacy Policy

We may update our Privacy Policy from time to time. We will notify you of any changes by posting the new Privacy Policy on this page.

We will let you know via email and/or a prominent notice on our Service, prior to the change becoming effective and update the “effective date” at the top of this Privacy Policy.

You are advised to review this Privacy Policy periodically for any changes. Changes to this Privacy Policy are effective when they are posted on this page.

#### 14\. Contact Us

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please contact us:  
By email: [privacy@embedsocial.com.](mailto:privacy@embedsocial.com)
